# **Michel Bravo**

### **Software Engineer**

**SUMMARY** 

Creative software engineer with two years of experience as Web Developer and IT Specialist. Proactive solving problems and contributing to project improvement. Motivated to advance and expand my skill set through challenging projects. Strong skills include frontend development with React.js or Vue.js and backend development with Express.js.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Cuspinera SURL**, Havana, Cuba (Remote) — Frontend Developer - Freelance

OCT 2022 - JAN 2023

**Skills:** Tailwind CSS · ECommerce · Node.js · React.js · Next.js

## **Telecommunications Company of Cuba S.A (ETECSA),** Havana, Cuba (Hybrid) — Full-stack Developer - Full Time

MAY 2022 - DEC 2022

**Skills:** Node.js · React.js · Next.js · NestJS · MongoDB

## Information Technology and Automation Company (ATI), Havana, Cuba (On-site) — IT Specialist - Full Time

NOV 2020 - MAY 2022

**Skills:** Network Administration  $\cdot$  Technical Support  $\cdot$  Microsoft Office  $\cdot$ 

Active Directory · Database Administration

## **Group of Entrepreneurs "Golden bulls"**, Havana, Cuba (Remote) — Full-stack Developer - Freelance

MAR 2021 - FEB 2022

**Skills:** Vue.js · Express.js · MySQL · JavaScript · Node.js

#### **EDUCATION**

## Technological University of Havana" José Antonio Echeverría", CUJAE, Havana, Cuba — Computer Software Engineering

SEP 2015 - NOV 2020

**Completion of studies:** Library of visual components of teaching calendars for the web.

Lake Charles, LA 70605
<<(123) 456-7890>>
mbravosarria@gmail.com
My Website · LinkedIn · GitHub

#### **SKILLS**

Full-stack Developer

- Javascript
- CSS
- SASS
- Node.js
- React.js
- Next.js
- Vue.js
- Express.js
- NestJS
- SQL
- MySQL
- MongoDB

#### IT Specialist

- Network Administration
- Technical Support
- Microsoft Office
- Active Directory
- Database Administration

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

JavaScript Algorithms and Data StructuresfreeCodeCamp

Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp

#### **LANGUAGES**

English, Spanish